RG 005, Office of the Governor Records
Governor Records, Office of the
- Series 1. Executive Clerk, 1820-1985
  - William F. Siering, Jr. Files, 1946-1985
    - T001494
      - Appointments, 1958-1985
        - Parole Evaluation Techniques and Rehabilitation, Commission on, 1973-1975 (Box 14)
        - Personnel and Administration, Commissioner of, 1967-1977 (Box 14)
        - Personnel Appeal Board, 1957-1977 (Box 14)
        - Personnel Policy Board, 1967-1976 (Box 14)
        - Petroleum Products Control Commission, 1971-1974 (Box 14)
        - Pharmacy, Commission of, 1969-1977 (Box 14)
        - Physical Therapists, Connecticut State Board of Examiners, 1969-1980 (Box 14)
        - Planning and Energy Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
        - Plumbing and Piping Work Examining Board, 1971-1977 (Box 14)
        - Podiatry, Connecticut Board of Examiners in, 1971-1976 (Box 14)
        - Policy and Management, Secretary of, 1977 August 3 (Box 14)
        - Polish Appointments, undated (Box 14)
        - Port Authority Study Commission, 1969 June -August, undated (Box 14)
        - Power Facility Evaluation Council, 1971-1977; 2 folders (Box 15)
        - Presidential Candidates, Commission to Study Procedures for Nomination of, 1969 July-October (Box 15)
        - Private Pension Funds, Regulation of, 1974 June 10 (Box 15)
        - Probate Judicial Conduct, Council on, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
        - Probate Laws, Commission to study and report on a Revision of the, 1967 June-October (Box 15)
        - Professional Standards Review Council, Statewide, 1976 April 30 (Box 15)
        - Psychologists, Board of Examiners of, 1971-1977 (Box 15)
        - Public Concern, Board of, undated (Box 15)
        - Public Defender Services Commission, 1974-1980 (Box 15)
        - Public Expenditure Council, Connecticut, 1976 May 26 (Box 15)
        - Public Health Council, 1965-1977 (Box 15)
        - Public Safety, Commissioner of, 1978 December 29 (Box 15)
        - Public Service Company Bonding, Task Force on, 1975 October (Box 15)
        - Public Utilities Commission, 1955-1975 (Box 15)
        - Public Utilities Control Authority, 1975-1980 (Box 15)
        - Public Utilities Control Authority Reorganization Task Force, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
        - Public Utilities Jurisdiction, Task Force on, 1975 October 1 (Box 15)
        - Public Works, Citizen's Advisory Council on, 1958-1971 (Box 15)
        - Public Works Commissioner, 1967-1976 (Box 15)
        - Public Works Construction Projects Task Force, 1975 May (Box 15)
        - Radioactive Fallout on Food, Committee on the Effect of, 1962-1971 (Box 16)
        - Railroad Advisory Task Force, Governor's, 1974-1977 (Box 16)
        - Railroad Legal Investment Commission, 1961-1963 (Box 16)
        - Real Estate Commission, Connecticut, 1967-1975 (Box 16)
        - Reapportionment Commission, 1971 March-November (Box 16)
        - Redistricting the Senate, Bi-Partisan Committee to Study the Problems of, 1959-1961 (Box 16)
        - Reemployment, Commission on, 1975 December 11 (Box 16)
        - Refineries, Fact Finding Task Force on, 1974 April-July (Box 16)
        - Regional Community Colleges, Board of Trustees for, 1971-1977 (Box 16)
        - Regional House Council, 1977 March-October (Box 16)
        - Resources Priority Board, 1967-1971 (Box 16)
        - Restoration of Historic ASSETS, Committee for the, 1977 August 4 (Box 16)
        - Retirement System for Teachers and State Employees, Commission to Study the, 1974 May-November (Box 16)
        - Retirement Systems, Special Study Commission to Investigate the Nature and Extent of Any Abuses, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
        - Revenue Task Force, 1969 February-September (Box 16)
        - Right-of-Way Screening Committee, 1970-1977 (Box 16)
        - Sanitarians, State Board of Registration for, 1971-1977 (Box 16)
        - Scholarship Commission, State, 1965-1977; 2 folders (Box 16)
        - School Building Projects, Committee to Review Regulations Concerning Standards and Priorities for, 1976 June-July (Box 16)
        - School Construction Projects, State Grant Commitments for, 1977 June (Box 16)
        - School Finance Advisory Panel, 1977 May-July (Box 16)
        - School Finance and Equal opportunity of Educational Opportunity, Commission to Study, 1973-1977 (Box 16)
        - Selective Service, 1970-1976; 7 folders (Box 17)
        - Shell-Fish Commissioner, 1967-1971 (Box 17)
        - Sheriff, 1960-1975 (Box 17)
        - Social Services, Citizens' Advisory Committee on, 1975-1977 (Box 17)
        - Solicitation of Rides in Motor Vehicles, Committee to Make a Study of the, 1974 June-July (Box 17)
        - Solid waste Management Advisory Council, Connecticut, 1973 May-1977 (Box 17)
        - Southbury Training School, Board of Trustees of the, 1971-1976 (Box 17)
        - Spanish-Speaking, Governor's Council on Opportunities for the, 1972-1976 (Box 17)
        - Special Education Costs Commission, 1976 May-October (Box 17)
        - Special Revenue, Connecticut Commission on, 1971-1980; 2 folders (Box 18)
        - Standardization Committee, 1955-1977; 2 folders (Box 18)
        - State Building Program Committee, 1955-1971; 2 folders (Box 18)
        - State Colleges, Board of Trustees for the, 1971-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Elections Commission, 1974-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Employee Disabilities Retirement Medical Examining Board, 1971-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Employees' Group Insurance Commission, 1965-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Employees' Retirement Commission, 1967-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Employees' Suggestion Awards Board, 1963-1972 (Box 18)
        - State Employment and Training Council, 1980 August-November (Box 18)
        - State Governments Committees, Council, Council of, 1975-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Library Board, 1975-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Planning Council, 1967-1972 (Box 18)
        - State Planning and Development, Legislative Committee on, 1973-1977 (Box 18)
        - State Police Commissioner, 1959-1975 (Box 18)
        - State Properties Review Board, 1977 June 14 (Box 18)
        - State Revenue Task Force, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
        - State Student Financial Assistance Commission, 1977 July-October (Box 18)
        - Steamship Terminals, Commissioners of, 1953-1971 (Box 19)
        - Sterling Opera House Foundation, 1962-1977 (Box 19)
        - Structure of State Government, Committee on the, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
        - Student Loan Foundation, Connecticut, 1965-1977 (Box 19)
        - Subsurface Sewage Disposal System Examiners, State Board of, 1974 May-October (Box 19)
        - Tax Commissioner, 1955-1975 (Box 19)
        - Tax Reform, Governor's Commission on, 1972 June-December (Box 19)
        - Tax Structure, Bi-Partisan Legislative Committee to Study, 1961 November 22 (Box 19)
        - Teachers, Advisory Board on State Certification of, 1967-1977; 3 folders (Box 19)
        - Technical Colleges, State: Board of Trustees for, 1972-1980 (Box 19)
        - Television and Radio Service Examiners, State Board of, 1968-1977 (Box 19)
        - Thames River Valley Flood Control Commission, 1957-1976 (Box 19)
        - Toy Advisory Committee, Governor's, 1975 December 3 (Box 19)
        - Transportation, Commission of, 1969-1976 (Box 19)
        - Tree Protection Examining Board, 1971-1977 (Box 19)
        - Tri-State Regional Planning Council, 1973-1977 (Box 19)
        - Tri-State Traffic Safety Commission, 1961-1962 (Box 19)
        - Tri-State Transportation Commission, 1969-1971, undated (Box 19)
        - Tuberculosis Control, Hospital Care and Rehabilitation, Council on, 1969-1977 (Box 19)
        - Undercliff Mental Health Center, Board of Trustees for the, 1971-1972 (Box 19)
        - Unemployment Commissioner, 1966-1974 (Box 19)
        - Unemployment Compensation Act, State Advisory Council for the, 1969-1974; 2 folders (Box 19)
        - Uniform Legislation, Commission on, 1975 April-June (Box 20)
        - University of Connecticut, Board of Trustees of the, 1971-1977 (Box 20)
        - University of Connecticut Health Center, 1973-1976 (Box 20)
        - Utility Finance, Special Task Force on, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
        - Vacation-Travel Council, Governor's, 1970-1980; 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Venereal Disease, Governor's Task Force on, 1972 February-September (Box 20)
        - Veteran's Bonus Appeals Board, 1975 February-April (Box 20)
        - Veteran's Home and Hospital Commission, 1957-1977; 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Veterinary Medicine, School of, 1972-1977 (Box 20)
        - Veterinary Medicine for Connecticut Students, Commission to study Alternative Methods of Providing Opportunities in, 1975 October 1 (Box 20)
        - Veterinary Registration and Examination, State Board of, 1956-1980; 2 folders (Box 20)
        - Vocational Education, State Advisory Council on, 1963-1976 (Box 20)
        - Vocational and Career Education, Connecticut Advisory Council on, 1968-1980; 4 folders (Box 21)
        - Voluntary Action Council, 1972-1980 (Box 21)
        - Water Company Lands, Council on, 1975 June-November (Box 21)
        - Water Resources Commission, 1967-1971 (Box 21)
        - Weather Control Board, 1959-1979 (Box 21)
        - Welfare Commissioner, 1959-1975 (Box 21)
        - Welfare, Citizens' Advisory Committee on, 1955-1975; 3 folders (Box 21)
        - Welfare Services, Interstate Compact on, 1961-1973 (Box 21)
        - Well Drilling Board, Connecticut, 1969-1977 (Box 21)
        - White House Conference on Handicapped Individuals, 1976 January-May (Box 21)
        - Whitfield State Historical Museum, Henry, 1949-1967 (Box 21)
        - Whiting Forensic Institute, Advisory and Review Board for the, 1972-1977 (Box 21)
        - Willimantic Water Department, Special Policemen of the, 1974 July (Box 21)
        - Women Appointees, 1972-1974, undated; 2 folders (Box 21)
        - Women, Permanent Commission on the Status of, 1973-1980 (Box 22)
        - Workmen's Compensation Commissioners, 1956-1980; 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Workmen's Compensation System, Commission to Study and Make Recommendations concerning the, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
        - Master Lists, 1965-1981, undated; 8 folders (Box 22)
      - Bills, 1967-1982
        - 1967 General Assembly Session (Box 23)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1967 (Box 23)
        - 1969 General Assembly Session (Box 23)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1969 (Box 23)
        - 1971 General Assembly Session (Box 23)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1971 (Box 23)
        - 1971 General Assembly Special Session (Box 23)
          - For Governor's Action, 1971 June 9-August 18 (Box 23)
        - 1972 General Assembly Session (Box 23)
          - Appointments as a result of bills, 1972 April 18-May 24 (Box 23)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1972 (Box 23)
          - S.H.B. 8001, State Employees Raises, 1972 October 30 -November 14 (Box 23)
        - 1973 General Assembly Session (Box 23)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1973 (Box 23)
          - 4:B. 8382, Gas Tax, 1973 February 15-16 (Box 23)
        - 1974 General Assembly Session (Box 23)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1974 (Box 23)
          - Recall of Bills, 1972 March 28-1974 May 6 (Box 23)
        - 1975 General Assembly Session (Box 23)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1975 (Box 23)
          - Signed or Vetoed, 1975 March 5-August 8; 5 folders (Box 23)
        - 1976 General Assembly Session (Box 24)
          - Appointments as a result of bills, 1976 April 6-October, undated (Box 24)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1976; 2 folders (Box 24)
        - 1977 General Assembly Session (Box 24)
          - Appointments as a result of bills, 1977 June 30-July 15 (Box 24)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1977; 2 folders (Box 24)
          - H.B. 5022, Battle Bill, 1977 May 16-17, undated (Box 24)
          - Signed or Vetoed, 1977 February 3-July 14, undated; 2 folders (Box 24)
        - 1978 General Assembly Session (Box 24)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1978 (Box 24)
        - 1979 General Assembly Session (Box 24)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1979 (Box 24)
        - 1980 General Assembly Session (Box 24)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1980 (Box 24)
        - 1981 General Assembly Session (Box 24)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1981 (Box 24)
        - 1982 General Assembly Session (Box 24)
          - Engrossed Bills Received, 1982 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence, 1954-1980
        - General, 1954-1980, undated; 4 folders (Box 25)
        - Eighteen year old voting, 1971 (Box 25)
        - Equal rights for men and women (H.R. 1 of 1973 General Assembly) (Box 25)
        - Extraditions, 1971-1975 (Box 25)
        - Leases, 1973-1975, undated (Box 25)
        - Offers of rewards, 1972-1975 (Box 25)
        - Wiretap law, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
      - Executive Orders and Proclamations, 1946-1976 (Box 25)
        - Executive orders, 1972-1976 (Box 25)
        - Proclamations, 1946-1974, undated (Box 25)
      - Special Elections, 1971-1980
        - House of Representatives (Box 26)
          - 1st District, 1977 December-1979 September (Box 26)
          - 1st District, 1981 January-February (Box 26)
          - 17th District, 1979 December-1980 January (Box 26)
          - 32nd District, 1979 August -1980 January (Box 26)
          - 39th District, 1974 June-1977 December (Box 26)
          - 50th District, 1973 June-August (Box 26)
          - 89th District, 1979 December-1980 November (Box 26)
          - 110th District, 1979 August-1980 January (Box 26)
          - 118th District, 1978 April (Box 26)
          - 104th Districts, 1981 January-February (Box 26)
          - 127th District, 1972 September-1974 January (Box 26)
          - 140th District, 1977 December-1978 January (Box 26)
        - Senate (Box 26)
          - 1st District, 1979 August-1981 February (Box 26)
          - 34th District, 1979 August-1980 January (Box 26)
        - Judge of Probate (Box 26)
          - Enfield, 1972 December-1973 November (Box 26)
          - Essex, 1971 April -1979 February (Box 26)
          - Harwinton, 1974 January-July (Box 26)
          - Middletown, 1976 December-1980 February (Box 26)
          - Norwich, 1980 February-1981 June (Box 26)
          - Oxford, 1979 February-July (Box 26)
          - Plainfield, 1974 July-1975 June (Box 26)
          - Redding, 1979 February (Box 26)
          - Salisbury, 1979 June-July (Box 26)
          - Southington, 1975 June (Box 26)
          - Stafford, 1971 April-1977 December (Box 26)
          - Waterbury, 1971 January-April (Box 26)
          - Westbrook, 1980 February-July (Box 26)
      - Transmittal Sheets, 1971-1980
        - 1971 General Assembly Session, 1971 February 3-September 8; 3 folders (Box 27)
        - 1972 General Assembly Session, 1972 February 15-November 30; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - 1973 General Assembly Session, 1973 January-June 27; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - 1974 General Assembly Session, 1974 February 27-May 24; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - 1975 General Assembly Session, 1975 March 5-December 10; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - 1976 General Assembly Session, 1976 March 3-May 27; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - 1977 General Assembly Session, 1977 February 3-June 28; 2 folders (Box 27)
        - 1979 General Assembly Session, 1979 February 28-1980 January 3; 4 folders (Box 28)
        - 1980 General Assembly Session, 1980 March 26-April 28; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - 2006-048
      - Appointments, circa 1960-1989
        - Last name
          - A-Da (Box 1)
          - De-H (Box 2)
          - I-Z (Box 3)
        - Boards (Box 3)
          - Academic Awards - Health Services (Box 3)
          - Higher Education - Youth Council (Box 4)
- Series 3. Proclamations, 1630-1993
  - 1630-1749 (Volume Vol. 1)
  - 1750-1779 (Volume Vol. 2)
  - 1780-1817 (Volume Vol. 3)
  - 1818-1860 (Volume Vol. 4)
  - 1861-1900 (Volume Vol. 5)
  - 1901-1925 (Volume Vol. 6)
  - 1926-1948 (Volume Vol. 7)
  - 1947-1959 (Volume Vol. 8)
  - 1960-1968 (Volume Vol. 9)
  - 1969-1971 (Volume Vol. 10)
  - 1972-1973 (Volume Vol. 11)
  - 1973-1975 (Box Box 1)
  - 1976-1981 (Box Box 2)
  - 1981-1990 (Box Box 3)
  - 1991-1993 (Box Box 4)
- Series 4. Correspondence, 1811-1933
  - Incoming Letters, 1811-1933; T000004; 24.5 cubic feet
    - John Treadwell, 1811 (Box 1)
    - Roger Griswold, 1811-1812 (Box 1)
    - Oliver Wolcott, Jr.
      - 1819, 1820 April 17-1821 May 31 (Box 1)
      - 1821 June 4-1822 May 30 (Box 2)
      - 1822 June 1-1823 December 18 (Box 3)
      - 1824 January 1-1825 June 10 (Box 4)
      - 1825 July 1-1827 April 27 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous Resolutions, 1830-1832 (Box 6)
    - John S. Peters, 1832 June 4-1833 May 3 (Box 6)
    - Henry W. Edwards, 1833 May 4- 1834 May 7 (Box 6)
    - Samuel A. Foot, 1834 May 8-1835 May 4 (Box 6)
    - Henry W. Edwards
      - 1835 May 12-1837 May 15 (Box 7)
      - 1837 May 16-1838 April 23 (Box 8)
    - William W. Ellsworth, 1838 May 6-1842 May 3 (Box 8)
    - Chauncey F. Cleveland, 1842 May 6-1844 April 2 (Box 9)
    - Public documents from the Commonwealth of Virginia, 1842-1843 (Box 9)
    - Roger S. Baldwin, 1844 January 7-1846 March 31 (Box 10)
    - Isaac Toucey, 1846 May 30-December 9 (Box 10)
    - Clark Bissell, 1847 April 13-1849 January 24 (Box 10)
    - Joseph Trumbull, 1849 May 28-1850 April 10 (Box 10)
    - Writs of election, Judges of Probate (Seymour, Pond, Dutton), 1851-1854 (Box 11)
    - Thomas S. Seymour, 1850 January 7- 1853 October 13 (Box 11)
    - Charles H. Pond, 1854 April (Box 11)
    - Henry S. Dutton, 1854 May-1855 May 4 (Box 11)
    - William T. Minor, 1855 May 10-1857 April 23 (Box 11)
    - Alexander H. Holley, 1857 May 8-1858 April 26 (Box 11)
    - William A. Buckingham
      - 1858 April 1-1861 April 15 (Box 12)
      - 1861 April 16-August 26 (Box 13)
      - 1861 August 27-September 30 (Box 13B)
      - 1861 October-December (Box 14)
      - 1862 January-May (Box 15)
      - 1862 June 1-August 10 (Box 16)
      - 1862 August 11-September 15 (Box 17)
      - 1862 September 16-December 31 (Box 18)
      - 1863 January-April (Box 19)
      - 1863 May-August (Box 20)
      - 1863 September-November (Box 21)
      - 1863 December-1864 February (Box 22)
      - 1864 March-June (Box 23)
      - 1864 July-September (Box 24)
      - 1865 October-January (Box 25)
      - 1865 February-May (Box 26)
      - 1865 June-August (Box 27)
      - 1865 September-1866 February (Box 28)
      - 1866 March-April (Box 29)
    - Joseph R. Hawley (Box 29)
      - General correspondence, 1866 May-December (Box 29)
      - Applications and appointments, State Commissioner of Deeds, 1866 (Box 29)
      - Insane, 1866 (Box 29)
      - Applications and appointments, 1867 (Box 30)
      - Insane, deaf, or blind, 1867 January-April (Box 30)
    - James E. English (Box 30)
      - General correspondence, 1867-1869 April, undated (Box 30)
        Folders with the same date range are in both Boxes 30 and 31.
      - General correspondence, 1867-1869 April, undated (Box 31)
    - Marshall Jewell (Box 31)
      - General correspondence, 1869 May-1870 May (Box 31)
      - Applications and appointments, 1869 May-1870 April (Box 31)
      - Insane, deaf, blind, mute, 1869 May-1870 May (Box 31)
    - James E. English (Box 31)
      - Applications and appointments, 1870 May-1870 October (Box 31)
      - Insane, deaf, blind, mute, 1870 May-1871 May (Box 31)
    - Marshall Jewell (Box 32)
      - General correspondence, 1871 February-December (Box 32)
      - Insane, deaf, dumb, blind, 1871-1873 (Box 32)
      - General correspondence, 1872 January-1873 March (Box 33)
      - Claims against the United States, 1871-1873 (Box 33)
      - Appointments, 1871 May-1873 (Box 34)
    - Charles R. Ingersoll (Box 35)
      - General correspondence, 1873 May-December (Box 35)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients, 1873 (Box 35)
      - Appointments, 1837 March-December (Box 35)
      - General correspondence, 1874 January-June (Box 35)
      - General correspondence, 1874 July-December (Box 36)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients, 1874 (Box 36)
      - Appointments, 1874 (Box 36)
      - General correspondence, 1875 (Box 36)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients, 1875 (Box 36)
      - Appointments, 1875 (Box 37)
      - General correspondence, 1876 (Box 37)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients, 1876 (Box 37)
      - Appointments, 1876 (Box 37)
    - Richard D. Hubbard (Box 38)
      - General correspondence, 1877 (Box 38)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients, 1877 (Box 38)
      - Appointments, 1877 (Box 38)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients, 1878 (Box 39)
      - Appointments, 1878 (Box 39)
      - Replies to business survey, 1878 (Box 39)
      - Extradition requests from other states, 1878 (Box 39)
      - General correspondence, 1878 (Box 40)
    - Charles B. Andrews (Box 40)
      - General correspondence, 1879 (Box 40)
      - Appointments, 1879 (Box 40)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients (Box 40)
        - 1879 January-April (Box 40)
        - 1879 May-December (Box 41)
      - General correspondence, 1880 (Box 41)
      - Hospitals, asylums, and patients, 1880 (Box 42)
    - Hobart B. Bigelow (Box 42)
      - 1881 (Box 42)
      - 1882 (Box 43)
    - Thomas M. Waller (Box 43)
      - 1883 (Box 43)
      - 1884-1885 January (Box 44)
    - Henry B. Harrison (Box 44)
      - 1885 (Box 44)
      - 1886 (Box 45)
    - Phineas C. Lounsbury, 1887-1888 (Box 45)
    - Morgan G. Bulkeley, 1889-1893 (Box 46)
    - Luzon B. Morris, 1893-1895 (Box 47)
    - O. Vincent Coffin (Box 47)
      - 1895 (Box 47)
      - 1895-1897 (Box 48)
    - Lorrin A. Cooke, 1897-1899 (Box 49)
    - George E. Lounsbury, 1899-1901 (Box 49)
    - George P. McLean, 1901-1903 (Box 50)
    - Abiram Chamberlain, 1903-1905 (Box 51)
    - Henry Roberts, 1905-1907 (Box 52)
    - Rollin S. Woodruff, 1907-1909 (Box 52)
    - George L. Lilley, 1909 (Box 52)
    - Frank B. Weeks, 1909-1911 (Box 52)
    - Simeon E. Baldwin, 1911-1915 (Box 53)
    - Marcus H. Holcomb (Box 54)
      - 1915-1919 (Box 54)
      - 1919-1921 (Box 55)
    - Everett J. Lake, 1921-1923 (Box 55)
    - Charles A. Templeton, 1923-1925 (Box 56)
    - John H. Trumbull (Box 56)
      - 1925-1927 (Box 56)
      - 1927-1931 (Box 57)
    - Wilbur L. Cross, 1931-1933 (Box 57)
    - Miscellaneous and unfiled (Box 58-59)
  - Outgoing Letters, 1863-1911, 1925; T001257; 15 volumes and 1 letter
    Official Letter Book of Early Governors
    - William A. Buckingham
      - 1863 April-1864 January (Box Vol. 1)
      - 1864 January-April (Box Vol. 2)
      - 1863 July-1864 June (Box Vol. 3)
      - 1864 April-October (Box Vol. 4)
      - 1864 October-1865 July (Box Vol. 5)
      - 1865 May-1866 April (Box Vol. 6)
    - Marshall Jewell
      - 1871 May-1873 April (Box Vol. 7)
      - 1873 May-1876 December (Box Vol. 8)
    - Richard D. Hubbard
      - 1877 January-September (Box Vol. 9)
      - 1877 October-1879 January (Box Vol. 8)
    - Morgan G. Bulkeley (Prentice, Executive Secretary), 1889 January-1892 February (Box Vol. 10)
    - Luxon B. Morris, 1893-1895 February (Box Vol. 11)
    - O. Vincent Coffin
      - 1895 February-1896 November (Box Vol. 11)
      - 1896 November-1897 January (Box Vol. 12)
    - Lorrin A. Cooke, 1897-1898 March (Box Vol. 12)
    - Rollin S. Woodruff, 1907 January-1909 January (Box Vol. 13)
    - George L. Lilley and Frank B. Weeks, 1909 January-1910 July (Box Vol. 14)
    - Frank B. Weeks, 1910 July-1911 January (Box Vol. 15)
    - Hiram Bingham to Charles Hopkins Clark, Hartford Courant, 1925 January 8; 1 letter (Box 1)
  - Military Correspondence, 1832-1882; 8.5 cubic feet
    - Incoming Letters
      - John S. Peters, 1832 April 3-1833 April 29 (Box 84)
      - Henry W. Edwards, 1833 May 4-1834 March 4 (Box 84)